Lawrence Guyot, Jr. 130
People's Archive, MLK Library
Lawrence Guyot, Jr. Papers
1963-2006
People's Archive, MLK Library
130
33 Cubic Feet
The Lawrence Guyot Jr. papers span from 1887 to 2012, with the bulk dating from 1963 to 2006. They document Guyot's involvement in D.C. government, particularly his time serving as Advisory Neighborhood Commissioner in the LeDroit Park neighborhood and as a program monitor for the D.C. Department of Human Services' Office of Early Childhood Development. The papers address his activism for voting rights as well as neighborhood revitalization.
Biographical / Historical
Lawrence Thomas Guyot Jr. was born in Pass Christian, Mississippi, on July 17, 1939. He attended Tougaloo College in Tougaloo, MS. Guyot earned degrees in both chemistry and biology. While in college, he became involved with the Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee and traveled around the state conducting civil rights workshops and doing other organizing. Guyot was a vocal protester during the civil rights era beginning in the early 1960s. When Fannie Lou Hamer and two other activists were jailed in Winona, Mississippi for violating segregation laws when they sat in a train station reserved for whites, Guyot went to see that they be released. When Guyot asked why the trio had been mistreated, he was beaten and tortured for hours, and afterwards thrown into a cell. He was also jailed in the Mississippi State Penitentiary (also known as Parchman Farm).
He chaired the Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party (MFDP). The gains made by the Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party assisted in the passage of the Voting Rights Act of 1965. By 1968, Mr. Guyot had full credentials to the national convention as a member of the Mississippi delegation.
Guyot attended Rutgers School of Law and, after graduating in 1971, moved to Washington, where he did legal work for city agencies and was an informal adviser to Mayor Marion Barry. Guyot was a program monitor for the D.C. Department of Human Services' Office of Early Childhood Development. He spent the rest of his life in D.C. in both local and federal government positions. He fought for reform in the most underserved neighborhoods in D.C., including LeDroit Park. He was a supporter of Howard University as well.
Custodial History
Gift of Lawrence Guyot Jr.'s daughter, Julie Guyot-Diangone, in 2013.
Scope and Contents
The Lawrence Guyot, Jr. papers span from 1887 to 2012 with the bulk of the collection ranging from 1963 to 2006. The collection documents Guyot's involvement in D.C. government and activism for voting rights, neighborhood revitalization, as well as his time serving as Advisory Neighborhood Commissioner in the LeDroit Park neighborhood and as a program monitor for the D.C. Department of Human Services' Office of Early Childhood Development. Documents include flyers, correspondence, reports, briefings, printed material and subjects that appear include the D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, the D.C. Board of Zoning and Adjustments, the Council of D.C., the Advisory Neighborhood Commision, the Columbia Heights neighborhood, LeDroit Park, Howard University, and the Naitonal Capital Revitalization Corporation, among other subjects.
- Series 1
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ward One, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1987-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District of Columbia Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1987-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - LeDroit, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Howard University, 1989-2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Heights, 1996-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Flyers/Programs, 2001-2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Press Releases, 2004-2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Newsclippings, 2000-2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Magazines, 1989-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Verified Complaint Gloria A. Halcomb v. Office of the Sergeant of Arms, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Guy Mason Recreation Center, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Office of the Inspector General, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Women and the Civil Rights Movement Presentation, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee 50th Anniversary Conference, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Grimke, Archibald Right on the Scaffold, or the Martyrs of 1822, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Howard University Student Association, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Howard University Health Sciences, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Main Street Approach Training Presentation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Public Defender Service, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - WPFW Managers Report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - North Mississippi Rural Legal Services, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Request for Proposals Destination District: Strategic Development Plan including Design Guidelines, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Certified Trainers for Early Care and Education, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The H.D. Woodson Hoop Dreams Scholarship Funds, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - DC Democracy Fund, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - One Church One Child Foster Care, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Invitation to Presidential Inaugural, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - First Tuesdays Urban Institute, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Testimonies, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1887-2011 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1999-2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Columbia Heights, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Handouts/Programs, 1992-2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Flyers, 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2006 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Magazines, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Newsclippings, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Nonquitt Elevations and Floor plans, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Howard University, 1989-2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Equitable Development in Shaw Packet, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ward One Redistricting, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guyot's News You Can Use, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Office of Zoning and of Zoning Adjustment, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia Alcoholic Beverage Regulation Administration, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia Department of Human Services, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - District of Columbia Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - District of Columbia Department of Parks and Recreation Arts and Smarts Progress Report, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Power and Interdependence by Robert O. Keohane and Joseph S. Nye, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Neighborhood Action Initiative, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Explaining Cooperation Under Anarchy: Hypotheses and Strategies by Kenneth A. Oye, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Washington Regional Network for Livable communities, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Howard University General Assembly Meeting, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - City View Team Packet, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - District of Columbia Office of Zoning Adjustment Legal Documents, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Foldered Loose Printed Materials, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - George Washington University Seminar on the District of Columbia, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Flyers, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Programs/Informational Handouts, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Newclippings, 2001-2009 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - From the Desk of Guyot, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - DC Democracy Fund, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - District of Colombia Land Development Agency, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Howard University, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Council of the Disrtict of Colombia, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Loose Printed Material, 1999-2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Community Development (1 of 2), 1999-2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Community Development (2 of 2), 2001-2006 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Colombia Heights Development, 1999-2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Confederate Flag, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Legal Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - DRAFT Traffic Calming Study, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Politics, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Plan "H", 2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Government of the District of Colombia, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - DC Appleseed Center Report, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Killien Trial, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Florida Challenge, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Clintion v. Obama, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - DC USA Project Public Hearing Documents, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ward Zoning Packets, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Community Development Support Collaborative, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Child Care Management System, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New Clippings, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ward One Redistricting, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - DreamCity Theatre Production, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Youth Programs, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Community Outreach, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Court Services and Offender Supervision Agency, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization Documents 1 of 2, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization Documents 2 of 2, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The City of Saint Jude Information, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - MetroVoice Youth Entrepreneurs Program Inc., 2008 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Canisius College Correspondence, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Safer Foundation Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Medgar Evers Information, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - United States Senate Apology to Lynching Victims, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers and Clippings 1 of 2, 1999-2009 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers and Clippings 2 of 2, 1999-2009 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Magazines, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Legal Documents 1 of 3, 1975-2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Legal Documents 2 of 3, 1975-2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Legal Documents 3 of 3, 1975-2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Loose Correspondence, 1972-2009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Association, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - District of Columbia Regulatory Reform Project, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1990-2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization Documents, 1989-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Howard University Community Advisory Committee, 1999-2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Guyot Commissioner Campaign Flyers, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1963-2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Informational Handouts 1 of 2, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Informational Handouts 2 of 2, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Flyers, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Transgender Issues and Awareness 1 of 2, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Transgender Issues and Awareness 2 of 2, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Peoples Involvement Coorporation, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Flyers, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 2002-2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers and Clippings, 1983-2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Social Work Education for the Prevention and Treatment of Alcohol Use Disorders 1 of 4, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Social Work Education for the Prevention and Treatment of Alcohol Use Disorders 2 of 4, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Social Work Education for the Prevention and Treatment of Alcohol Use Disorders 3 of 4, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Social Work Education for the Prevention and Treatment of Alcohol Use Disorders 4 of 4, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - International Geriatric Documents 1 of 3, 1998-2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - International Geriatric Documents 2 of 3, 1998-2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - International Geriatric Documents 3 of 3, 1998-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for Political and Financial Accountability, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - LeDroit Park, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Howard University, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Columbia Heights, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Washington D.C. Issues, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The College Fund/ United Negro College Fund White House Invitation List, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Eleanor Holmes Norton, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pathways to Freedom, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Ward One Advisory Neighborhood Committee Redistricting Task Force, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - District of Columbia Zoning Commission Public Hearing 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - District of Columbia Zoning Commission Public Hearing 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Advanced Telecomunication Sercives in D.C., 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - One Stop Center Building Permit Applications, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Mississisppi Casino Newsclippings, 1991-1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 1 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 2 of 2, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Adams Morgan Alterantive Garage Analysis, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Newsclippings and Magazines, 1995-2005 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Flyers, 1993-2006 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Public Welfare Foundation Annual Report, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - U Street Block Party, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - CIA, Crack, and Our Communities Project, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Legal Documents, 2000-2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Association, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Heights Development, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters' D.C. Public School Campaign Flyers, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioner, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hawaiin Sovereignty, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Tivoli Square Fact Sheet, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Flyers and Informational Sheets, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Newsclippings and Magazines 1 of 2, 1999-2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Newsclippings and Magazines 2 of 2, 1999-2008 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Legal Documents, 1995-2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - The Voting Rights Act, 1971-2005 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Y2K Informational Packet, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - King's Dream and Obama's Promise, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - The History Makers, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Business Cards/Handouts/Notes/Clippings, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Government of the District of Columbia Documents, 2001-2007 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Loose Correspondence, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Arts and Smarts, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Revenue Plan, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - LeDroit Park Conserved, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Reentry Strategy for Adults in the District of Columbia, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pat Humphries - Event Flyers, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Job Search Tips, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for Political and Financial Accountability, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Implementing the Help America Vote Act, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 1986-2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Howard University, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Columbia Heights, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commisson, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commisson 1B 1 of 2, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commisson 1B 2 of 2, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Newsclippings and Magazines, 1998-2009 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases and Letters, 1996-2010 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Loose Correspondence, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ward One, 1985-2004 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Office of Planning, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Office of Zoning 1 of 3, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Office of Zoning 2 of 3, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Office of Zoning 3 of 3, 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Legal Documents, 1987-2004 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - H.R. 1345, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Regulation Administration, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1997-2005 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Programs/Brochures/Cards, 1998-2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Committee to Elect Guyot, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Informational Handouts, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Flyers, 1995-2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Loose Correspondence, 1974-2008 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Brief for Amici Curiae for Southern Civil Rights Movement, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners' Assembly, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1999-2004 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Howard University, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Department of Human Services, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Government of District of Columbia Office of Planning, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Newsclippings/Magazines/Press Releases, 1997-2008 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Youth Pride Incorporated Washington D.C. Management Information Placement System, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - District of Columbia Nurses Association Strike, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - National Black Leadership Roundtable, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Community Choir of LeDroit Park Christmas Caroling Selections, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lawrence Guyot: An Oral History, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Program Guide for Rotarians, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Anacostia Waterfront Initiative, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Obama Election Day 2008 Packet, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lincoln: The American International School In Buenos Aires, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Court Services and Offender Supervision Agency, 1997-2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - New Horizon Partners, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Proposal to Develop Parcels 19 - RO-20 and 32, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Environments Planning Guide 1 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Environments Planning Guide 2 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 1 of 2, 1994-2005 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B 2 of 2, 1994-2005 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1986-2005 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1996-2011 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Howard University, 2002-2009 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Georgetown University Medical Center, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Redevelopment Land Association Revitalization Corporation, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - LeDroit Park, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Heights, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Tivoli Square Fact Sheet, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1999-2005 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Democracy Fund, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Programs and Brochures, 1985-2011 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Flyers, 1996-2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Newsclippings/Magazines, 1989-2011 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Legal Documents, 1974-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Act to establish the National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Help America Vote Act, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Child Care and Education, 1991-2008 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pablo Martinez Board of Adjustment Applications, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Department of Housing and Community Development, 1998-2009 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1988-2003 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1995-2008 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Milkwaukee Area Technical College, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Preservation League, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Economic Development Plan for Washington D.C., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Academic Papers, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Peace, Justice, and Unity Program Script, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Gerontology, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - College Classes, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Child Care and Education, 2002-2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Afro-American/Cultural/Technological/Scientific Olympics, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence Guyot Interview, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights History Education, 1999-2006 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1996-2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights: New Board Member Orientation Meeting, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Howard University Central Campus Masterplan, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics Public Hearing, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics Public Hearing, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics Public Hearing, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Protecting Voting Rights, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Land Disposition and Development Agreement, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Newsclippings/Magazines, 1991-2008 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - North Mississippi Rural Legal Services, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Flyers/Brochures/Handouts, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Southern Institute for Education and Research, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Draft Ward 1 Plan, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Guyot's News and Views that You Can Use, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Guyot Campaign Materials, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Flyers, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Government Documents, 1986-2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1988-2007 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Resolution, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Legal Documents, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Howard, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)